{
  "uniqueId": "7",
  "showDictionaryLink": true,
  "name": "JLPT N3 Reading Quiz",
  "category": "JLPT",
  "article": "a",
  "instructions": "Type the reading of the below word in Hiragana!",
  "cards": [
    {"meaning":"love","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"愛","answer":["あい"]},
    {"meaning":"love,affection","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"愛情","answer":["あいじょう"]},
    {"meaning":"sign,signal","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"合図","answer":["あいず"]},
    {"meaning":"to love","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"愛する","answer":["あいする"]},
    {"meaning":"companion,partner,company","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"相手","answer":["あいて"]},
    {"meaning":"lamplight,light (in general),brightness","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"明かり","answer":["あかり"]},
    {"meaning":"room,time to spare,emptiness","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"空き","answer":["あき"]},
    {"meaning":"obvious,evident,clear","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"明らか","answer":["あきらか"]},
    {"meaning":"devil,demon,evil spirit","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"悪魔","answer":["あくま"]},
    {"meaning":"to dawn,to become daylight","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"明ける","answer":["あける"]},
    {"meaning":"to give,to present,to award","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"与える","answer":["あたえる"]},
    {"meaning":"to be hit,to be successful,to be equivalent to","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"当たる","answer":["あたる"]},
    {"meaning":"to hit,to apply a patch","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"当てる","answer":["あてる"]},
    {"meaning":"not very (used as adverb),not much","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"余り","answer":["あまり","あんまり"]},
    {"meaning":"error","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"誤り","answer":["あやまり"]},
    {"meaning":"new,fresh,novel","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"新た","answer":["あらた"]},
    {"meaning":"to express,to show,to reveal","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"表す","answer":["あらわす"]},
    {"meaning":"to show,to indicate,to display","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"現す","answer":["あらわす"]},
    {"meaning":"embodiment,materialization","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"現れ","answer":["あらわれ"]},
    {"meaning":"(1) to appear,to come in sight,to become visible,(2) to express oneself","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"現れる","answer":["あらわれる"]},
    {"meaning":"to be,to have","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"有る","answer":["ある"]},
    {"meaning":"to join together,to be opposite,to face,to unite","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"合わせる","answer":["あわせる"]},
    {"meaning":"memorization,learning by heart","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"暗記","answer":["あんき"]},
    {"meaning":"stability,equilibrium","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"安定","answer":["あんてい"]},
    {"meaning":"unexpected,surprising","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"意外","answer":["いがい"]},
    {"meaning":"going","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"行き","answer":["いき","ゆき"]},
    {"meaning":"breath,tone","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"息","answer":["いき"]},
    {"meaning":"living thing,animal","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"生き物","answer":["いきもの"]},
    {"meaning":"doctor,physician","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"医師","answer":["いし"]},
    {"meaning":"intention,purpose","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"意思","answer":["いし"]},
    {"meaning":"consciousness,senses","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"意識","answer":["いしき"]},
    {"meaning":"ago,since,before,previous","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"以前","answer":["いぜん"]},
    {"meaning":"greatness","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"偉大","answer":["いだい"]},
    {"meaning":"(sl) to embrace,to hug,to harbour,to entertain","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"抱く","answer":["いだく","だく"]},
    {"meaning":"pain,ache,sore,grief,distress","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"痛み","answer":["いたみ"]},
    {"meaning":"place,situation,position,location","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"位置","answer":["いち"]},
    {"meaning":"moment,time","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"一時","answer":["いちじ"]},
    {"meaning":"all at once","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"一度に","answer":["いちどに"]},
    {"meaning":"(the) market (as a concept)","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"市場","answer":["いちば"]},
    {"meaning":"best,first,number one","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"一番","answer":["いちばん"]},
    {"meaning":"a house,a home,a family,a household","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"一家","answer":["いっか"]},
    {"meaning":"a species,a kind,a variety","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"一種","answer":["いっしゅ"]},
    {"meaning":"whole life,a lifetime,all through life","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"一生","answer":["いっしょう"]},
    {"meaning":"(1) one object,one body,(2) what on earth?,really?,(3) generally","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"一体","answer":["いったい"]},
    {"meaning":"(1) on the other hand,(2) meanwhile,(3) only,simple,in turn","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"一方","answer":["いっぽう"]},
    {"meaning":"dozing,nodding off","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"居眠り","answer":["いねむり"]},
    {"meaning":"command,decree,life,destiny","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"命","answer":["いのち"]},
    {"meaning":"violation (of law),transgression,infringement,breach","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"違反","answer":["いはん"]},
    {"meaning":"living room (western style)","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"居間","answer":["いま"]},
    {"meaning":"before long,even now","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"今に","answer":["いまに"]},
    {"meaning":"at any time,soon","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"今にも","answer":["いまにも"]},
    {"meaning":"since,henceforth","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"以来","answer":["いらい"]},
    {"meaning":"so to speak","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"言わば","answer":["いわば"]},
    {"meaning":"retire","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"引退","answer":["いんたい"]},
    {"meaning":"quotation,citation","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"引用","answer":["いんよう"]},
    {"meaning":"on top of","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"上","answer":["うえ","うわ","かみ","じょう"]},
    {"meaning":"to receive,to get,to accept,to take","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"受け取る","answer":["うけとる"]},
    {"meaning":"to move,to shift","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"動かす","answer":["うごかす"]},
    {"meaning":"cattle,cow","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"牛","answer":["うし"]},
    {"meaning":"to lose,to part with","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"失う","answer":["うしなう"]},
    {"meaning":"afterwards","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"後","answer":["あと","うしろ","ご","のち"]},
    {"meaning":"to doubt,to distrust,to be suspicious of,to suspect","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"疑う","answer":["うたがう"]},
    {"meaning":"inside","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"内","answer":["うち"]},
    {"meaning":"birth,birth-place","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"生まれ","answer":["うまれ"]},
    {"meaning":"to be sold","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"売れる","answer":["うれる"]},
    {"meaning":"fortune,luck","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"運","answer":["うん"]},
    {"meaning":"to drive","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"運転","answer":["うんてん"]},
    {"meaning":"to exercise","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"運動","answer":["うんどう"]},
    {"meaning":"smiling face","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"笑顔","answer":["えがお"]},
    {"meaning":"to get,to gain,to win","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"得る","answer":["える","うる"]},
    {"meaning":"circle,money","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"円","answer":["えん","まる"]},
    {"meaning":"speech,address","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"演説","answer":["えんぜつ"]},
    {"meaning":"honourable","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"御","answer":["お","ご"]},
    {"meaning":"old age,old person,the old,the aged","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"老い","answer":["おい"]},
    {"meaning":"to overtake,to catch up (with)","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"追い付く","answer":["おいつく"]},
    {"meaning":"king,ruler,sovereign,monarch","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"王","answer":["おう"]},
    {"meaning":"to chase,to run after","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"追う","answer":["おう"]},
    {"meaning":"king","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"王様","answer":["おうさま"]},
    {"meaning":"prince","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"王子","answer":["おうじ"]},
    {"meaning":"crossing","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"横断","answer":["おうだん"]},
    {"meaning":"to finish","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"終える","answer":["おえる"]},
    {"meaning":"very,much,greatly","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"大いに","answer":["おおいに"]},
    {"meaning":"rich family,distinguished family","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"大家","answer":["おおや"]},
    {"meaning":"to occur,to happen","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"起こる","answer":["おこる"]},
    {"meaning":"to obtain,to reap,to pay,to supply,to accept","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"収める","answer":["おさめる"]},
    {"meaning":"to fear,to be afraid of","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"恐れる","answer":["おそれる"]},
    {"meaning":"terrible,dreadful","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"恐ろしい","answer":["おそろしい"]},
    {"meaning":"mutual,reciprocal,each other","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"お互い","answer":["おたがい"]},
    {"meaning":"man","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"男の人","answer":["おとこのひと"]},
    {"meaning":"stomach","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"お腹","answer":["おなか"]},
    {"meaning":"lunch,noon","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"お昼","answer":["おひる"]},
    {"meaning":"to meet (humble)","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"お目に掛かる","answer":["おめにかかる"]},
    {"meaning":"memories,recollections,reminiscence","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"思い出","answer":["おもいで"]},
    {"meaning":"mainly,primarily","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"主に","answer":["おもに"]},
    {"meaning":"unintentional,spontaneous","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"思わず","answer":["おもわず"]},
    {"meaning":"swimming","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"泳ぎ","answer":["およぎ"]},
    {"meaning":"to make a decision, to hand down a verdict","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"下す","answer":["くだす"]},
    {"meaning":"meeting,assembly,party,association,club","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"会","answer":["かい"]},
    {"meaning":"counter for occurrences","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"回","answer":["かい"]},
    {"meaning":"injury,harm,evil influence,damage","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"害","answer":["がい"]},
    {"meaning":"member,the membership","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"会員","answer":["かいいん"]},
    {"meaning":"picture","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"絵画","answer":["かいが"]},
    {"meaning":"foreign,abroad,overseas","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"海外","answer":["かいがい"]},
    {"meaning":"account,finance,accountant","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"会計","answer":["かいけい"]},
    {"meaning":"settlement,solution,resolution","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"解決","answer":["かいけつ"]},
    {"meaning":"meeting,assembly","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"会合","answer":["かいごう"]},
    {"meaning":"diplomacy","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"外交","answer":["がいこう"]},
    {"meaning":"start,commencement,beginning","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"開始","answer":["かいし"]},
    {"meaning":"outing,going out","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"外出","answer":["がいしゅつ"]},
    {"meaning":"painter,artist","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"画家","answer":["がか"]},
    {"meaning":"to hold or carry under or in the arms","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"抱える","answer":["かかえる"]},
    {"meaning":"chemistry","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"化学","answer":["かがく"]},
    {"meaning":"official,duty,person in charge","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"係","answer":["かかり"]},
    {"meaning":"to take (e.g. time, money, etc),to hang","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"掛かる","answer":["かかる"]},
    {"meaning":"furniture","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"家具","answer":["かぐ"]},
    {"meaning":"learning,scholarship,erudition,knowledge","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"学","answer":["がく"]},
    {"meaning":"certainty,reliability,soundness","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"確実","answer":["かくじつ"]},
    {"meaning":"scholar","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"学者","answer":["がくしゃ"]},
    {"meaning":"study,learning","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"学習","answer":["がくしゅう"]},
    {"meaning":"affirmation,confirmation","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"確認","answer":["かくにん"]},
    {"meaning":"scholarship,study,learning","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"学問","answer":["がくもん"]},
    {"meaning":"to be lacking","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"欠ける","answer":["かける"]},
    {"meaning":"the past,bygone days,the previous","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"過去","answer":["かこ"]},
    {"meaning":"loan,lending","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"貸し","answer":["かし"]},
    {"meaning":"housework,domestic chores","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"家事","answer":["かじ"]},
    {"meaning":"singer","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"歌手","answer":["かしゅ"]},
    {"meaning":"number,figure","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"数","answer":["かず","すう"]},
    {"meaning":"to count","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"数える","answer":["かぞえる"]},
    {"meaning":"persons,this and that,here and there,everywhere","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"方々","answer":["かたがた","ほうぼう"]},
    {"meaning":"to talk,to tell,to recite","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"語る","answer":["かたる"]},
    {"meaning":"win,victory","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"勝ち","answer":["かち"]},
    {"meaning":"energy,liveliness","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"活気","answer":["かっき"]},
    {"meaning":"term (school)","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"学期","answer":["がっき"]},
    {"meaning":"shape,form,posture,suitability","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"格好","answer":["かっこう"]},
    {"meaning":"action,activity","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"活動","answer":["かつどう"]},
    {"meaning":"conjugation,practical use","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"活用","answer":["かつよう"]},
    {"meaning":"to be sad,to mourn for,to regret","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"悲しむ","answer":["かなしむ"]},
    {"meaning":"(not) always,(not) necessarily,(not) all,(not) entirely","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"必ずしも","answer":["かならずしも"]},
    {"meaning":"(1) gold,(2) gold general (shogi) (abbr)","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"金","answer":["かね","きん"]},
    {"meaning":"rich man","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"金持ち","answer":["かねもち"]},
    {"meaning":"to mind,to care about,to be concerned about","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"構う","answer":["かまう"]},
    {"meaning":"god","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"神","answer":["かみ"]},
    {"meaning":"(school) subject,curriculum,course","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"科目","answer":["かもく"]},
    {"meaning":"Sky","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"空","answer":["そら","から"]},
    {"meaning":"thinking,thought,ideas,intention","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"考え","answer":["かんがえ"]},
    {"meaning":"sense,sensation","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"感覚","answer":["かんかく"]},
    {"meaning":"audience,spectator(s)","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"観客","answer":["かんきゃく"]},
    {"meaning":"sightseeing","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"観光","answer":["かんこう"]},
    {"meaning":"observation,survey","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"観察","answer":["かんさつ"]},
    {"meaning":"feeling,sense,impression","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"感じ","answer":["かんじ"]},
    {"meaning":"emotion(s),feeling(s),sentiment","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"感情","answer":["かんじょう"]},
    {"meaning":"to feel,to sense,to experience","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"感じる","answer":["かんじる"]},
    {"meaning":"admiration,Well done!","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"感心","answer":["かんしん"]},
    {"meaning":"concern,interest","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"関心","answer":["かんしん"]},
    {"meaning":"to concern,to be related","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"関する","answer":["かんする"]},
    {"meaning":"(1) complete,completion,(2) perfection,accomplishment","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"完成","answer":["かんせい"]},
    {"meaning":"perfection,completeness","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"完全","answer":["かんぜん"]},
    {"meaning":"being deeply moved,excitement,impression,deep emotion","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"感動","answer":["かんどう"]},
    {"meaning":"relation,connection,relevance","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"関連","answer":["かんれん"]},
    {"meaning":"member of the Diet, congress or parliament","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"議員","answer":["ぎいん"]},
    {"meaning":"Diet,congress,parliament","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"議会","answer":["ぎかい"]},
    {"meaning":"period,term","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"期間","answer":["きかん"]},
    {"meaning":"organ,mechanism,facility,engine","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"機関","answer":["きかん"]},
    {"meaning":"climate","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"気候","answer":["きこう"]},
    {"meaning":"birthplace","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"生地","answer":["きじ"]},
    {"meaning":"article,news story,report,account","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"記事","answer":["きじ"]},
    {"meaning":"reporter","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"記者","answer":["きしゃ"]},
    {"meaning":"expectation,anticipation,hope","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"期待","answer":["きたい"]},
    {"meaning":"returning home","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"帰宅","answer":["きたく"]},
    {"meaning":"chairman","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"議長","answer":["ぎちょう"]},
    {"meaning":"to notice,to recognize,to become aware of","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"気付く","answer":["きづく"]},
    {"meaning":"to be pleased with,to suit","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"気に入る","answer":["きにいる"]},
    {"meaning":"entry,filling in of forms","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"記入","answer":["きにゅう"]},
    {"meaning":"commemoration,memory","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"記念","answer":["きねん"]},
    {"meaning":"function,faculty","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"機能","answer":["きのう"]},
    {"meaning":"contribution,donation","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"寄付","answer":["きふ"]},
    {"meaning":"settlement,conclusion,regulation,rule","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"決まり","answer":["きまり"]},
    {"meaning":"-like,-looking,-looked","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"気味","answer":["きみ"]},
    {"meaning":"question,problem,doubt,guess","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"疑問","answer":["ぎもん"]},
    {"meaning":"globe,sphere,ball","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"球","answer":["きゅう","たま"]},
    {"meaning":"absorption,suction,attraction","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"吸収","answer":["きゅうしゅう"]},
    {"meaning":"rapid (e.g. progress)","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"急速","answer":["きゅうそく"]},
    {"meaning":"","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"急に","answer":["きゅうに"]},
    {"meaning":"salary,wages","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"給料","answer":["きゅうりょう"]},
    {"meaning":"text book","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"教科書","answer":["きょうかしょ"]},
    {"meaning":"supply,provision","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"供給","answer":["きょうきゅう"]},
    {"meaning":"teacher (classroom)","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"教師","answer":["きょうし"]},
    {"meaning":"emphasis,stress,stressed point","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"強調","answer":["きょうちょう"]},
    {"meaning":"commonness,community","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"共通","answer":["きょうつう"]},
    {"meaning":"cooperation,association,collaboration,joint","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"共同","answer":["きょうどう"]},
    {"meaning":"be afraid,dread,dismay,terror","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"恐怖","answer":["きょうふ"]},
    {"meaning":"herculean strength,mountain carrier-guide","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"強力","answer":["きょうりょく"]},
    {"meaning":"court lady,lady in waiting","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"局","answer":["きょく"]},
    {"meaning":"cloth,piece,cut,chop","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"切れ","answer":["きれ"]},
    {"meaning":"(1) to cut well,to be sharp,(2) to break (off)","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"切れる","answer":["きれる"]},
    {"meaning":"argument,discussion,dispute","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"議論","answer":["ぎろん"]},
    {"meaning":"(1) silver,silver coin,silver paint","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"銀","answer":["ぎん"]},
    {"meaning":"amount of money","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"金額","answer":["きんがく"]},
    {"meaning":"present day","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"近代","answer":["きんだい"]},
    {"meaning":"(by) chance,unexpectedly,suddenly","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"偶然","answer":["ぐうぜん"]},
    {"meaning":"concrete,tangible,material","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"具体","answer":["ぐたい"]},
    {"meaning":"down-train (going away from Tokyo)","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"下り","answer":["くだり"]},
    {"meaning":"pain,agony","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"苦痛","answer":["くつう"]},
    {"meaning":"class,group,team,set","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"組","answer":["くみ"]},
    {"meaning":"association,union","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"組合","answer":["くみあい"]},
    {"meaning":"to put together","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"組む","answer":["くむ"]},
    {"meaning":"living,livelihood,subsistence,circumstances","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"暮らし","answer":["くらし"]},
    {"meaning":"to live,to get along","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"暮らす","answer":["くらす"]},
    {"meaning":"painful,difficult","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"苦しい","answer":["くるしい"]},
    {"meaning":"to suffer,to groan,to be worried","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"苦しむ","answer":["くるしむ"]},
    {"meaning":"year end,sunset,nightfall,end","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"暮れ","answer":["くれ"]},
    {"meaning":"troubles,hardships","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"苦労","answer":["くろう"]},
    {"meaning":"to append,to sum up,to add (up)","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"加える","answer":["くわえる"]},
    {"meaning":"to join in,to accede to,to increase,to gain in (influence)","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"加わる","answer":["くわわる"]},
    {"meaning":"Below","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"下","answer":["した","げ","しも"]},
    {"meaning":"plan","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"計","answer":["けい"]},
    {"meaning":"to plan","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"計画","answer":["けいかく"]},
    {"meaning":"condition,state,business (condition)","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"景気","answer":["けいき"]},
    {"meaning":"experience","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"経験","answer":["けいけん"]},
    {"meaning":"warning,advice","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"警告","answer":["けいこく"]},
    {"meaning":"go by the way,via","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"経由","answer":["けいゆ"]},
    {"meaning":"defect,fault,deficiency","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"欠陥","answer":["けっかん"]},
    {"meaning":"determination,resolution","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"決心","answer":["けっしん"]},
    {"meaning":"absence,non-attendance","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"欠席","answer":["けっせき"]},
    {"meaning":"decision,determination","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"決定","answer":["けってい"]},
    {"meaning":"faults,defect,weakness","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"欠点","answer":["けってん"]},
    {"meaning":"smoke,fumes","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"煙","answer":["けむり"]},
    {"meaning":"opinion,point of view","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"見解","answer":["けんかい"]},
    {"meaning":"limit,bound","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"限界","answer":["げんかい"]},
    {"meaning":"cash,ready money,mercenary,self-interested","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"現金","answer":["げんきん"]},
    {"meaning":"language","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"言語","answer":["げんご"]},
    {"meaning":"present,up to now,nowadays,modern times,current","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"現在","answer":["げんざい"]},
    {"meaning":"reality","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"現実","answer":["げんじつ"]},
    {"meaning":"present condition,existing state,status quo","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"現状","answer":["げんじょう"]},
    {"meaning":"nowadays,modern times,present-day","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"現代","answer":["げんだい"]},
    {"meaning":"be found,aim,estimate,guess,approx","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"見当","answer":["けんとう"]},
    {"meaning":"actual spot,scene,scene of the crime","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"現場","answer":["げんば","げんじょう"]},
    {"meaning":"right,privilege","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"権利","answer":["けんり"]},
    {"meaning":"language,word","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"語","answer":["ご"]},
    {"meaning":"good luck,fortune","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"幸運","answer":["こううん"]},
    {"meaning":"success,passing (e.g. exam),eligibility","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"合格","answer":["ごうかく"]},
    {"meaning":"scene,spectacle","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"光景","answer":["こうけい"]},
    {"meaning":"sum total,total amount","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"合計","answer":["ごうけい"]},
    {"meaning":"advertisement","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"広告","answer":["こうこく"]},
    {"meaning":"company,friendship,association,society,acquaintance","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"交際","answer":["こうさい"]},
    {"meaning":"the latter","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"後者","answer":["こうしゃ"]},
    {"meaning":"factory","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"工場","answer":["こうじょう","こうば"]},
    {"meaning":"organization,composition","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"構成","answer":["こうせい"]},
    {"meaning":"high speed,high gear","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"高速","answer":["こうそく"]},
    {"meaning":"action,conduct,behaviour,mobilization","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"行動","answer":["こうどう"]},
    {"meaning":"robbery,burglary","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"強盗","answer":["ごうとう"]},
    {"meaning":"happiness,blessedness","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"幸福","answer":["こうふく"]},
    {"meaning":"fairness,impartial,justice","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"公平","answer":["こうへい"]},
    {"meaning":"to exceed,to cross over,to cross","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"越える","answer":["こえる"]},
    {"meaning":"misunderstanding","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"誤解","answer":["ごかい"]},
    {"meaning":"language study","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"語学","answer":["ごがく"]},
    {"meaning":"breath,respiration","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"呼吸","answer":["こきゅう"]},
    {"meaning":"national language","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"国語","answer":["こくご"]},
    {"meaning":"national,people,citizen","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"国民","answer":["こくみん"]},
    {"meaning":"to go over (e.g. with audience)","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"越す","answer":["こす"]},
    {"meaning":"state,country,nation","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"国家","answer":["こっか"]},
    {"meaning":"National Diet,parliament,congress","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"国会","answer":["こっかい"]},
    {"meaning":"bone fracture","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"骨折","answer":["こっせつ"]},
    {"meaning":"thing,matter,fact,circumstances","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"事","answer":["こと"]},
    {"meaning":"to refuse,to decline,to dismiss","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"断る","answer":["ことわる"]},
    {"meaning":"liking,taste,choice","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"好み","answer":["このみ"]},
    {"meaning":"to like,to prefer","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"好む","answer":["このむ"]},
    {"meaning":"wheat","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"小麦","answer":["こむぎ"]},
    {"meaning":"hut,cabin,shed,(animal) pen","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"小屋","answer":["こや"]},
    {"meaning":"to kill","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"殺す","answer":["ころす"]},
    {"meaning":"to fall down,to fall over","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"転ぶ","answer":["ころぶ"]},
    {"meaning":"now,this time,lately","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"今回","answer":["こんかい"]},
    {"meaning":"from now on,hereafter","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"今後","answer":["こんご"]},
    {"meaning":"difficulty,distress","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"困難","answer":["こんなん"]},
    {"meaning":"Today","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"今日","answer":["きょう","こんにち"]},
    {"meaning":"engagement,betrothal","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"婚約","answer":["こんやく"]},
    {"meaning":"difference,variation","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"差","answer":["さ"]},
    {"meaning":"highest,supreme,the most","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"最高","answer":["さいこう"]},
    {"meaning":"property,fortune,assets","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"財産","answer":["ざいさん"]},
    {"meaning":"last,final,closing","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"最終","answer":["さいしゅう"]},
    {"meaning":"in the middle of","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"最中","answer":["さいちゅう"]},
    {"meaning":"talent,ability","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"才能","answer":["さいのう"]},
    {"meaning":"happiness,blessedness","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"幸い","answer":["さいわい"]},
    {"meaning":"work,operation,manufacturing,fatigue duty","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"作業","answer":["さぎょう"]},
    {"meaning":"last (year),yesterday","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"昨","answer":["さく"]},
    {"meaning":"work,opus,performance,production","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"作品","answer":["さくひん"]},
    {"meaning":"produce (e.g. agricultural),crops","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"作物","answer":["さくもつ","さくぶつ"]},
    {"meaning":"alcohol,sake","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"酒","answer":["さけ"]},
    {"meaning":"to support, sustain, prop up","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"支える","answer":["ささえる"]},
    {"meaning":"to point,to put up umbrella,to play","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"指す","answer":["さす"]},
    {"meaning":"seat","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"座席","answer":["ざせき"]},
    {"meaning":"author,writer,novelist,artist","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"作家","answer":["さっか"]},
    {"meaning":"composition,setting (of music)","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"作曲","answer":["さっきょく"]},
    {"meaning":"discrimination,distinction,differentiation","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"差別","answer":["さべつ"]},
    {"meaning":"manners,etiquette,propriety","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"作法","answer":["さほう"]},
    {"meaning":"varied,various","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"様々","answer":["さまざま"]},
    {"meaning":"to awaken","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"覚ます","answer":["さます"]},
    {"meaning":"to wake,to wake up","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"覚める","answer":["さめる"]},
    {"meaning":"(1) left and right,(2) influence,control,domination","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"左右","answer":["さゆう"]},
    {"meaning":"furthermore,again,after all,more and more,moreover","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"更に","answer":["さらに"]},
    {"meaning":"to leave,to go away","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"去る","answer":["さる"]},
    {"meaning":"participation","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"参加","answer":["さんか"]},
    {"meaning":"reference,consultation","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"参考","answer":["さんこう"]},
    {"meaning":"walk,stroll","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"散歩","answer":["さんぽ","さんぽする"]},
    {"meaning":"Four","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"四","answer":["し","よん"]},
    {"meaning":"happiness,good fortune,luck,blessing","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"幸せ","answer":["しあわせ"]},
    {"meaning":"jet aeroplane","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"ジェット機","answer":["ジェットき","じぇっとき"]},
    {"meaning":"immediately,readily,directly","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"直に","answer":["じかに"]},
    {"meaning":"equation,formula,ceremony","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"式","answer":["しき"]},
    {"meaning":"earnestly,immediately,exactly","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"直","answer":["じき"]},
    {"meaning":"time,season,period","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"時期","answer":["じき"]},
    {"meaning":"payment,allowance","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"支給","answer":["しきゅう"]},
    {"meaning":"event,affair,incident","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"事件","answer":["じけん"]},
    {"meaning":"instant,time,moment","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"時刻","answer":["じこく"]},
    {"meaning":"suicide","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"自殺","answer":["じさつ"]},
    {"meaning":"fact,truth,reality","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"事実","answer":["じじつ"]},
    {"meaning":"expenditure,expenses","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"支出","answer":["ししゅつ"]},
    {"meaning":"circumstances,consideration,conditions,situation,reasons","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"事情","answer":["じじょう"]},
    {"meaning":"nature,spontaneous","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"自然","answer":["しぜん"]},
    {"meaning":"thought,idea","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"思想","answer":["しそう"]},
    {"meaning":"preparation","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"支度","answer":["したく"]},
    {"meaning":"intimate,close (e.g. friend)","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"親しい","answer":["したしい"]},
    {"meaning":"Seven","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"七","answer":["しち","なな"]},
    {"meaning":"quality,nature (of person)","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"質","answer":["しつ"]},
    {"meaning":"unemployment","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"失業","answer":["しつぎょう"]},
    {"meaning":"experiment","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"実験","answer":["じっけん"]},
    {"meaning":"implementation,materialization,realization","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"実現","answer":["じつげん"]},
    {"meaning":"practice,performance,execution (e.g. program),realization","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"実行","answer":["じっこう"]},
    {"meaning":"practical,actual condition,status quo","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"実際","answer":["じっさい"]},
    {"meaning":"indeed,truly,surely","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"実に","answer":["じつに"]},
    {"meaning":"as a matter of fact,by the way","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"実は","answer":["じつは"]},
    {"meaning":"disappointment,despair","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"失望","answer":["しつぼう"]},
    {"meaning":"branch store (office)","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"支店","answer":["してん"]},
    {"meaning":"automatic,self-motion","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"自動","answer":["じどう"]},
    {"meaning":"thing,article,goods,dignity,article (goods),counter for meal courses","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"品","answer":["しな","ひん"]},
    {"meaning":"rule,control,direction","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"支配","answer":["しはい"]},
    {"meaning":"payment","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"支払","answer":["しはらい"]},
    {"meaning":"to pay","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"支払う","answer":["しはらう"]},
    {"meaning":"death,mortality","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"死亡","answer":["しぼう"]},
    {"meaning":"funds,capital","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"資本","answer":["しほん"]},
    {"meaning":"sisters","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"姉妹","answer":["しまい","きょうだい"]},
    {"meaning":"business,office work","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"事務","answer":["じむ"]},
    {"meaning":"to denote,to show,to point out,to indicate","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"示す","answer":["しめす"]},
    {"meaning":"debt,loan,liabilities","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"借金","answer":["しゃっきん"]},
    {"meaning":"week","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"週","answer":["しゅう"]},
    {"meaning":"Ten","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"十","answer":["じゅう","とお"]},
    {"meaning":"week,weekly","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"週間","answer":["しゅうかん"]},
    {"meaning":"serious,important,grave,weighty","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"重大","answer":["じゅうだい"]},
    {"meaning":"resident,housing","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"住宅","answer":["じゅうたく"]},
    {"meaning":"concentration,focusing the mind","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"集中","answer":["しゅうちゅう"]},
    {"meaning":"income,receipts,revenue","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"収入","answer":["しゅうにゅう"]},
    {"meaning":"citizens,inhabitants,residents,population","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"住民","answer":["じゅうみん"]},
    {"meaning":"important,momentous,essential,principal,major","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"重要","answer":["じゅうよう"]},
    {"meaning":"surgical operation","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"手術","answer":["しゅじゅつ"]},
    {"meaning":"Prime Minister","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"首相","answer":["しゅしょう"]},
    {"meaning":"means,way,measure","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"手段","answer":["しゅだん"]},
    {"meaning":"attendance,presence","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"出席","answer":["しゅっせき"]},
    {"meaning":"to depart","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"出発","answer":["しゅっぱつ"]},
    {"meaning":"capital city","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"首都","answer":["しゅと"]},
    {"meaning":"housewife,mistress","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"主婦","answer":["しゅふ"]},
    {"meaning":"chief,main,principal,major","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"主要","answer":["しゅよう"]},
    {"meaning":"demand,request","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"需要","answer":["じゅよう"]},
    {"meaning":"variety,kind,type","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"種類","answer":["しゅるい"]},
    {"meaning":"favourable,doing well,O.K.,all right","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"順調","answer":["じゅんちょう"]},
    {"meaning":"turn (in line),order of things","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"順番","answer":["じゅんばん"]},
    {"meaning":"use,application,employment,utilization","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"使用","answer":["しよう"]},
    {"meaning":"","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"小","answer":["しょう"]},
    {"meaning":"obstacle,impediment (fault),damage","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"障害","answer":["しょうがい"]},
    {"meaning":"passenger","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"乗客","answer":["じょうきゃく","じょうかく"]},
    {"meaning":"proceeding to the capital (Tokyo)","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"上京","answer":["じょうきょう"]},
    {"meaning":"noon,mid-day","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"正午","answer":["しょうご"]},
    {"meaning":"honesty,integrity,frankness","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"正直","answer":["しょうじき"]},
    {"meaning":"common sense","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"常識","answer":["じょうしき"]},
    {"meaning":"daughter,young lady,virgin,maiden,little girl","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"少女","answer":["しょうじょ","おとめ"]},
    {"meaning":"just a minute,small quantity","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"少々","answer":["しょうしょう"]},
    {"meaning":"to produce,to yield,to result from,to arise,to be generated","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"生じる","answer":["しょうじる"]},
    {"meaning":"invitation","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"招待","answer":["しょうたい"]},
    {"meaning":"improvement,advance,progress","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"上達","answer":["じょうたつ"]},
    {"meaning":"superiority,first class,very good","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"上等","answer":["じょうとう"]},
    {"meaning":"trader,shopkeeper,merchant","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"商人","answer":["しょうにん","あきうど","あきんど","あきゅうど","あきびと"]},
    {"meaning":"boys,juveniles","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"少年","answer":["しょうねん"]},
    {"meaning":"trade,business,commerce,transaction,occupation","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"商売","answer":["しょうばい"]},
    {"meaning":"consumption,expenditure","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"消費","answer":["しょうひ"]},
    {"meaning":"commodity,article of commerce,goods,stock,merchandise","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"商品","answer":["しょうひん"]},
    {"meaning":"fire fighting,fire department","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"消防","answer":["しょうぼう"]},
    {"meaning":"information,(military) intelligence","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"情報","answer":["じょうほう"]},
    {"meaning":"queen","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"女王","answer":["じょおう"]},
    {"meaning":"employment","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"職","answer":["しょく"]},
    {"meaning":"occupation,business","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"職業","answer":["しょくぎょう"]},
    {"meaning":"to have a meal","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"食事","answer":["しょくじ"]},
    {"meaning":"commodity,foodstuff","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"食品","answer":["しょくひん"]},
    {"meaning":"food,foodstuff","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"食物","answer":["しょくもつ"]},
    {"meaning":"appetite (for food)","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"食欲","answer":["しょくよく"]},
    {"meaning":"food","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"食料","answer":["しょくりょう"]},
    {"meaning":"woman,girl","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"女子","answer":["じょし","おなご"]},
    {"meaning":"helper,helpmeet,assistant,tutor","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"助手","answer":["じょしゅ"]},
    {"meaning":"books","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"書物","answer":["しょもつ"]},
    {"meaning":"actress","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"女優","answer":["じょゆう"]},
    {"meaning":"processing,dealing with,treatment,disposition,disposal","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"処理","answer":["しょり"]},
    {"meaning":"documents,official papers","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"書類","answer":["しょるい"]},
    {"meaning":"notice","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"知らせ","answer":["しらせ"]},
    {"meaning":"going on to university","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"進学","answer":["しんがく"]},
    {"meaning":"nerve,sensitivity","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"神経","answer":["しんけい"]},
    {"meaning":"traffic lights,signal,semaphore","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"信号","answer":["しんごう"]},
    {"meaning":"artificial,manmade,human work,human skill,artificiality","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"人工","answer":["じんこう"]},
    {"meaning":"serious","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"深刻","answer":["しんこく"]},
    {"meaning":"race (of people)","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"人種","answer":["じんしゅ"]},
    {"meaning":"to believe,to place trust in","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"信じる","answer":["しんじる"]},
    {"meaning":"(human) life (i.e. conception to death)","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"人生","answer":["じんせい"]},
    {"meaning":"fresh","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"新鮮","answer":["しんせん"]},
    {"meaning":"worry,concern,anxiety,care","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"心配","answer":["しんぱい"]},
    {"meaning":"character,personality,person,man,personage,talented man","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"人物","answer":["じんぶつ"]},
    {"meaning":"progress,development","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"進歩","answer":["しんぽ"]},
    {"meaning":"close friend,buddy","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"親友","answer":["しんゆう"]},
    {"meaning":"confidence,dependence,credit,faith","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"信用","answer":["しんよう"]},
    {"meaning":"reliance,trust,confidence","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"信頼","answer":["しんらい"]},
    {"meaning":"mentality","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"心理","answer":["しんり"]},
    {"meaning":"mankind,humanity","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"人類","answer":["じんるい"]},
    {"meaning":"figure (e.g. Fig 1),drawing,picture,illustration","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"図","answer":["ず"]},
    {"meaning":"numeral,figure","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"数字","answer":["すうじ"]},
    {"meaning":"the end of,powder","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"末","answer":["すえ","うら"]},
    {"meaning":"to open, to become empty","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"空く","answer":["あく","すく"]},
    {"meaning":"to surpass,to outstrip,to excel","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"優れる","answer":["すぐれる"]},
    {"meaning":"anything of,not one bit","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"少しも","answer":["すこしも"]},
    {"meaning":"to pass,to spend,to go through,to tide over","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"過ごす","answer":["すごす"]},
    {"meaning":"to advance,to promote,to hasten","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"進める","answer":["すすめる"]},
    {"meaning":"headache","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"頭痛","answer":["ずつう"]},
    {"meaning":"all,the whole,entirely,in general,wholly","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"全て","answer":["すべて"]},
    {"meaning":"to be finished","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"済ませる","answer":["すませる"]},
    {"meaning":"height,stature","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"背","answer":["せい","せ"]},
    {"meaning":"(logical) true,regular","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"正","answer":["せい"]},
    {"meaning":"(1) draft (beer),(2) raw,unprocessed","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"生","answer":["せい","なま","き"]},
    {"meaning":"sex,gender","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"性","answer":["せい"]},
    {"meaning":"character,personality","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"性格","answer":["せいかく"]},
    {"meaning":"accurate,punctuality,exactness,authenticity,veracity","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"正確","answer":["せいかく"]},
    {"meaning":"restriction,restraint,limitation","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"制限","answer":["せいげん"]},
    {"meaning":"production,manufacture","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"生産","answer":["せいさん"]},
    {"meaning":"due form,official,formality","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"正式","answer":["せいしき"]},
    {"meaning":"mind,soul,heart,spirit,intention","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"精神","answer":["せいしん"]},
    {"meaning":"adult","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"成人","answer":["せいじん"]},
    {"meaning":"growth,grow to adulthood","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"成長","answer":["せいちょう"]},
    {"meaning":"system,institution,organization","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"制度","answer":["せいど"]},
    {"meaning":"youth,young man","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"青年","answer":["せいねん"]},
    {"meaning":"raw food","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"生物","answer":["せいぶつ"]},
    {"meaning":"life,existence","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"生命","answer":["せいめい"]},
    {"meaning":"duty,responsibility","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"責任","answer":["せきにん"]},
    {"meaning":"world,society","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"世間","answer":["せけん"]},
    {"meaning":"theory","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"説","answer":["せつ"]},
    {"meaning":"absolute,unconditional,absoluteness","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"絶対","answer":["ぜったい"]},
    {"meaning":"to condemn,to blame,to criticize","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"責める","answer":["せめる"]},
    {"meaning":"to look after","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"世話","answer":["せわ"]},
    {"meaning":"all,whole,entire,complete,overall,pan","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"全","answer":["ぜん"]},
    {"meaning":"all members (unanimity),all hands,the whole crew","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"全員","answer":["ぜんいん"]},
    {"meaning":"country-wide,nation-wide,whole country,national","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"全国","answer":["ぜんこく"]},
    {"meaning":"the other day,a few days ago","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"先日","answer":["せんじつ"]},
    {"meaning":"the former","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"前者","answer":["ぜんしゃ"]},
    {"meaning":"(1) player (in game),(2) team","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"選手","answer":["せんしゅ"]},
    {"meaning":"advance,drive,progress","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"前進","answer":["ぜんしん"]},
    {"meaning":"(1) wholly,entirely,completely,(2) not at all (with neg. verb)","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"全然","answer":["ぜんぜん"]},
    {"meaning":"whole,entirety,whatever (is the matter)","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"全体","answer":["ぜんたい"]},
    {"meaning":"increase,addition","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"増加","answer":["ぞうか"]},
    {"meaning":"succession,inheritance","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"相続","answer":["そうぞく"]},
    {"meaning":"consultation,discussion","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"相談","answer":["そうだん"]},
    {"meaning":"suitable,fair,tolerable,proper","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"相当","answer":["そうとう"]},
    {"meaning":"speed,velocity,rate","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"速度","answer":["そくど"]},
    {"meaning":"to pour (into),to irrigate,to pay,to fill,to feed (e.g. a fire)","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"注ぐ","answer":["そそぐ","つぐ"]},
    {"meaning":"to raise (child),to be brought up,to grow (up)","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"育つ","answer":["そだつ"]},
    {"meaning":"to furnish,to provide for,to equip,to install","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"備える","answer":["そなえる"]},
    {"meaning":"side,edge,third person","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"側","answer":["そば","かわ","がわ"]},
    {"meaning":"existence,being","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"存在","answer":["そんざい"]},
    {"meaning":"rice field","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"田","answer":["た"]},
    {"meaning":"other (esp. places and things)","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"他","answer":["た","ほか"]},
    {"meaning":"pair,couple,set","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"対","answer":["たい"]},
    {"meaning":"","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"大","answer":["だい"]},
    {"meaning":"stand,rack,table,support","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"台","answer":["だい"]},
    {"meaning":"physical education,gymnastics,athletics","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"体育","answer":["たいいく"]},
    {"meaning":"convention,tournament,mass meeting,rally","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"大会","answer":["たいかい"]},
    {"meaning":"atmosphere","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"大気","answer":["たいき"]},
    {"meaning":"price,payment,cost,charge","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"代金","answer":["だいきん"]},
    {"meaning":"ambassador","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"大使","answer":["たいし"]},
    {"meaning":"considerable,great,important,significant,a big deal","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"大した","answer":["たいした"]},
    {"meaning":"to face,to confront,to oppose","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"対する","answer":["たいする"]},
    {"meaning":"great war,great battle","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"大戦","answer":["たいせん"]},
    {"meaning":"majority,mostly,generally","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"大半","answer":["たいはん"]},
    {"meaning":"representative,representation,delegation,type,example,model","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"代表","answer":["だいひょう"]},
    {"meaning":"awful,dreadful,terrible,very","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"大変","answer":["たいへん"]},
    {"meaning":"sun,solar","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"太陽","answer":["たいよう"]},
    {"meaning":"flatness,level,smooth,calm,plain","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"平ら","answer":["たいら"]},
    {"meaning":"representation,agency,proxy,deputy,agent","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"代理","answer":["だいり"]},
    {"meaning":"continent","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"大陸","answer":["たいりく"]},
    {"meaning":"to throw down,to beat,to bring down,to blow down","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"倒す","answer":["たおす"]},
    {"meaning":"mutual,reciprocal","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"互い","answer":["たがい"]},
    {"meaning":"house,home,husband","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"宅","answer":["たく"]},
    {"meaning":"to ascertain","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"確かめる","answer":["たしかめる"]},
    {"meaning":"more or less,somewhat,a little,some","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"多少","answer":["たしょう"]},
    {"meaning":"to help,to save,to rescue","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"助ける","answer":["たすける"]},
    {"meaning":"battle,fight,struggle,conflict","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"戦い","answer":["たたかい"]},
    {"meaning":"to fight,to battle,to combat","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"戦う","answer":["たたかう"]},
    {"meaning":"at once,immediately,directly,in person","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"直ちに","answer":["ただちに"]},
    {"meaning":"to stand up","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"立ち上がる","answer":["たちあがる"]},
    {"meaning":"standpoint,position,situation","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"立場","answer":["たちば"]},
    {"meaning":"to pass,to lapse","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"経つ","answer":["たつ"]},
    {"meaning":"to reach,to get to","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"達する","answer":["たっする"]},
    {"meaning":"another person,unrelated person,outsider,stranger","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"他人","answer":["たにん","あだびと"]},
    {"meaning":"(1) seed,(2) material,(3) cause,source","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"種","answer":["たね","しゅ"]},
    {"meaning":"handbreadth,bundle","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"束","answer":["たば"]},
    {"meaning":"counter for occurrences","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"度","answer":["たび","ど"]},
    {"meaning":"travel,trip,journey","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"旅","answer":["たび"]},
    {"meaning":"even number,couple,man and wife,friend","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"偶","answer":["たま"]},
    {"meaning":"trial,test","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"試し","answer":["ためし"]},
    {"meaning":"to attempt,to test","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"試す","answer":["ためす"]},
    {"meaning":"news,tidings,information,correspondence,letter","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"便り","answer":["たより"]},
    {"meaning":"step,stair,flight of steps,grade,rank,level","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"段","answer":["だん"]},
    {"meaning":"unit,denomination,credit (in school)","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"単位","answer":["たんい"]},
    {"meaning":"word,vocabulary,(usually) single-character word","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"単語","answer":["たんご"]},
    {"meaning":"youth,young man","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"男子","answer":["だんし"]},
    {"meaning":"mere,simple,sheer","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"単なる","answer":["たんなる"]},
    {"meaning":"simply,merely,only,solely","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"単に","answer":["たんに"]},
    {"meaning":"earth","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"地","answer":["ち"]},
    {"meaning":"(social) position,status","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"地位","answer":["ちい"]},
    {"meaning":"basement,underground","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"地下","answer":["ちか"]},
    {"meaning":"difference,discrepancy","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"違い","answer":["ちがい"]},
    {"meaning":"(phrase) sure,no mistaking it,for certain","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"違いない","answer":["ちがいない"]},
    {"meaning":"lately,recently,nowadays","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"近頃","answer":["ちかごろ"]},
    {"meaning":"the earth","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"地球","answer":["ちきゅう"]},
    {"meaning":"lateness,late coming","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"遅刻","answer":["ちこく"]},
    {"meaning":"prefectural governor","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"知事","answer":["ちじ"]},
    {"meaning":"knowledge,information","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"知識","answer":["ちしき"]},
    {"meaning":"father","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"父親","answer":["ちちおや"]},
    {"meaning":"intelligence,brains","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"知能","answer":["ちのう"]},
    {"meaning":"area,locality,district,region,the coast","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"地方","answer":["ちほう","じかた"]},
    {"meaning":"tea","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"茶","answer":["ちゃ"]},
    {"meaning":"middle","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"中","answer":["なか","ちゅう"]},
    {"meaning":"annotation,explanatory note","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"注","answer":["ちゅう"]},
    {"meaning":"middle school,junior high school","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"中学","answer":["ちゅうがく"]},
    {"meaning":"(1) used,second-hand,old","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"中古","answer":["ちゅうこ"]},
    {"meaning":"suspension,stoppage,discontinuance,interruption","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"中止","answer":["ちゅうし"]},
    {"meaning":"parking (e.g. car)","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"駐車","answer":["ちゅうしゃ"]},
    {"meaning":"lunch,midday meal","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"昼食","answer":["ちゅうしょく"]},
    {"meaning":"center,core,heart,pivot,emphasis,balance","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"中心","answer":["ちゅうしん"]},
    {"meaning":"notice,attention,observation","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"注目","answer":["ちゅうもく"]},
    {"meaning":"order,request","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"注文","answer":["ちゅうもん"]},
    {"meaning":"long time period","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"長期","answer":["ちょうき"]},
    {"meaning":"tune,tone,key","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"調子","answer":["ちょうし"]},
    {"meaning":"top,summit,peak","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"頂上","answer":["ちょうじょう"]},
    {"meaning":"passage through,passing","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"通過","answer":["つうか"]},
    {"meaning":"commuting to school","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"通学","answer":["つうがく"]},
    {"meaning":"passage,passing","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"通行","answer":["つうこう"]},
    {"meaning":"to run to,to lead to,to communicate,to understand","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"通じる","answer":["つうじる"]},
    {"meaning":"correspondence,communication,news,signal","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"通信","answer":["つうしん"]},
    {"meaning":"to be caught,to be arrested","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"捕まる","answer":["つかまる"]},
    {"meaning":"tiredness,fatigue","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"疲れ","answer":["つかれ"]},
    {"meaning":"moon,month","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"月","answer":["つき"]},
    {"meaning":"association,socializing,fellowship","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"付き合い","answer":["つきあい"]},
    {"meaning":"in succession,one by one","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"次々","answer":["つぎつぎ"]},
    {"meaning":"to attach,to join,to add,to append","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"付ける","answer":["つける"]},
    {"meaning":"earth,soil","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"土","answer":["つち"]},
    {"meaning":"sequel,continuation","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"続き","answer":["つづき"]},
    {"meaning":"(1) service,duty,business,responsibility,task,(2) Buddhist religious services","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"勤め","answer":["つとめ"]},
    {"meaning":"(1) service,duty,(2) Buddhist religious services","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"務め","answer":["つとめ"]},
    {"meaning":"always,constantly","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"常に","answer":["つねに"]},
    {"meaning":"crime,fault,indiscretion","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"罪","answer":["つみ"]},
    {"meaning":"to pile up","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"積もる","answer":["つもる"]},
    {"meaning":"companion,company","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"連れ","answer":["つれ"]},
    {"meaning":"meeting,rendezvous,encounter","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"出会い","answer":["であい"]},
    {"meaning":"to meet by chance,to come across,to happen to encounter","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"出会う","answer":["であう"]},
    {"meaning":"fixed term","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"定期","answer":["ていき"]},
    {"meaning":"degree,amount,grade,standard,of the order of (following a number)","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"程度","answer":["ていど"]},
    {"meaning":"incident,affair,happening,event","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"出来事","answer":["できごと"]},
    {"meaning":"to fit,to suit","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"適する","answer":["てきする"]},
    {"meaning":"pertinent,appropriate,adequate,relevance","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"適切","answer":["てきせつ"]},
    {"meaning":"moderate","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"適度","answer":["てきど"]},
    {"meaning":"applying","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"適用","answer":["てきよう"]},
    {"meaning":"if at all possible","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"出来るだけ","answer":["できるだけ"]},
    {"meaning":"sleight of hand,conjuring trick,magic,juggling","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"手品","answer":["てじな"]},
    {"meaning":"help,helper,assistant","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"手伝い","answer":["てつだい"]},
    {"meaning":"time,labour","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"手間","answer":["てま"]},
    {"meaning":"weather","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"天候","answer":["てんこう"]},
    {"meaning":"electron","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"電子","answer":["でんし"]},
    {"meaning":"nature,spontaneity","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"天然","answer":["てんねん"]},
    {"meaning":"question,query","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"問い","answer":["とい"]},
    {"meaning":"identity,sameness,similarity","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"同一","answer":["どういつ"]},
    {"meaning":"at that time,in those days","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"当時","answer":["とうじ"]},
    {"meaning":"simultaneous(ly),concurrent,same time,synchronous","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"同時","answer":["どうじ"]},
    {"meaning":"arrival","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"到着","answer":["とうちゃく"]},
    {"meaning":"identical,equal to,same (kind),like","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"同様","answer":["どうよう"]},
    {"meaning":"road,highway","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"道路","answer":["どうろ"]},
    {"meaning":"to let pass,to overlook,to continue","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"通す","answer":["とおす"]},
    {"meaning":"in accordance with ~,following ~,~ Street,~ Avenue","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"通り","answer":["とおり"]},
    {"meaning":"to pass,to pass through","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"通り過ぎる","answer":["とおりすぎる"]},
    {"meaning":"city","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"都会","answer":["とかい"]},
    {"meaning":"(1) time,hour,(2) occasion,moment","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"時","answer":["とき"]},
    {"meaning":"to unfasten","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"解く","answer":["とく","ほどく"]},
    {"meaning":"pride,triumph,prosperity","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"得意","answer":["とくい"]},
    {"meaning":"reading","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"読書","answer":["どくしょ"]},
    {"meaning":"to come untied,to come apart","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"解ける","answer":["とける"]},
    {"meaning":"mountain-climbing","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"登山","answer":["とざん"]},
    {"meaning":"town,city,municipal,urban","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"都市","answer":["とし"]},
    {"meaning":"months and years","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"年月","answer":["としつき","ねんげつ"]},
    {"meaning":"books","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"図書","answer":["としょ"]},
    {"meaning":"old people,the aged","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"年寄","answer":["としより"]},
    {"meaning":"to close (e.g. book, eyes),to shut","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"閉じる","answer":["とじる"]},
    {"meaning":"plot of land,lot,soil","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"土地","answer":["とち"]},
    {"meaning":"abruptly,suddenly,unexpectedly,all at once","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"突然","answer":["とつぜん"]},
    {"meaning":"to jump out,to rush out,to fly out","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"飛び出す","answer":["とびだす"]},
    {"meaning":"to fasten,to turn off,to detain","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"留める","answer":["とめる","とどめる"]},
    {"meaning":"friend,companion,pal","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"友","answer":["とも"]},
    {"meaning":"sharing with,participate in","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"共に","answer":["ともに"]},
    {"meaning":"to take up,to pick up,to disqualify,to confiscate,to deprive","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"取り上げる","answer":["とりあげる"]},
    {"meaning":"great effort,exertion,endeavour,effort","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"努力","answer":["どりょく"]},
    {"meaning":"to come off,to be taken off,to be removed","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"取れる","answer":["とれる"]},
    {"meaning":"name,reputation","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"名","answer":["な"]},
    {"meaning":"subject,contents,matter,substance,detail,import","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"内容","answer":["ないよう"]},
    {"meaning":"to drain,to float,to shed (blood, tears),to cruise (e.g. taxi)","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"流す","answer":["ながす"]},
    {"meaning":"middle,half,semi,halfway,partly","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"半ば","answer":["なかば"]},
    {"meaning":"stream,current","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"流れ","answer":["ながれ"]},
    {"meaning":"to stream,to flow,to run (ink),to be washed away","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"流れる","answer":["ながれる"]},
    {"meaning":"et cetera,etc.,and the like","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"等","answer":["など","とう"]},
    {"meaning":"what","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"何","answer":["なん","なに"]},
    {"meaning":"something","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"何か","answer":["なにか"]},
    {"meaning":"to suit,to match,to become,to be like","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"似合う","answer":["にあう"]},
    {"meaning":"poor (at),weak (in),dislike (of)","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"苦手","answer":["にがて"]},
    {"meaning":"day, sun","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"日","answer":["ひ","にち"]},
    {"meaning":"ordinary,regular,everyday,usual","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"日常","answer":["にちじょう"]},
    {"meaning":"sunlight","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"日光","answer":["にっこう"]},
    {"meaning":"daytime,broad daylight","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"日中","answer":["にっちゅう"]},
    {"meaning":"Japan","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"日本","answer":["にっぽん","にほん"]},
    {"meaning":"to hospitalise","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"入院","answer":["にゅういん"]},
    {"meaning":"to enter school or university","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"入学","answer":["にゅうがく"]},
    {"meaning":"entrance,admission,entering","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"入場","answer":["にゅうじょう"]},
    {"meaning":"sign of life","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"人気","answer":["にんき"]},
    {"meaning":"human being,man,person","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"人間","answer":["にんげん"]},
    {"meaning":"to extract,to omit,to surpass,to draw out,to unplug","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"抜く","answer":["ぬく"]},
    {"meaning":"to come out,to fall out,to be omitted","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"抜ける","answer":["ぬける"]},
    {"meaning":"value,price,cost","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"値","answer":["ね","あたい"]},
    {"meaning":"price,cost","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"値段","answer":["ねだん"]},
    {"meaning":"zeal,enthusiasm","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"熱心","answer":["ねっしん"]},
    {"meaning":"nuts!,enthusiasm,zeal,mania","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"熱中","answer":["ねっちゅう"]},
    {"meaning":"year","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"年間","answer":["ねんかん"]},
    {"meaning":"whole year,always,everyday","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"年中","answer":["ねんじゅう"]},
    {"meaning":"age,era,period,date","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"年代","answer":["ねんだい"]},
    {"meaning":"age,years","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"年齢","answer":["ねんれい"]},
    {"meaning":"field","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"野","answer":["の"]},
    {"meaning":"being skilled in,nicely,properly","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"能","answer":["のう"]},
    {"meaning":"ability,faculty","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"能力","answer":["のうりょく"]},
    {"meaning":"to leave (behind, over),to bequeath,to save,to reserve","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"残す","answer":["のこす"]},
    {"meaning":"remnant,residue,remaining,left-over","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"残り","answer":["のこり"]},
    {"meaning":"to place on (something),to take on board,to give a ride","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"乗せる","answer":["のせる"]},
    {"meaning":"wish,desire,(a) hope","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"望み","answer":["のぞみ"]},
    {"meaning":"to desire,to wish for,to see,to command (a view of)","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"望む","answer":["のぞむ"]},
    {"meaning":"place,field (physics)","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"場","answer":["ば"]},
    {"meaning":"delivery,distribution","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"配達","answer":["はいたつ"]},
    {"meaning":"to measure,to weigh,to survey","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"計る","answer":["はかる"]},
    {"meaning":"(personal) bankruptcy","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"破産","answer":["はさん"]},
    {"meaning":"origin,beginning","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"始まり","answer":["はじまり"]},
    {"meaning":"to unfasten,to remove","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"外す","answer":["はずす"]},
    {"meaning":"20 years old,20th year","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"二十","answer":["はたち"]},
    {"meaning":"work,labor","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"働き","answer":["はたらき"]},
    {"meaning":"discovery,detection,finding","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"発見","answer":["はっけん"]},
    {"meaning":"issue (publications)","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"発行","answer":["はっこう"]},
    {"meaning":"departure of a vehicle","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"発車","answer":["はっしゃ"]},
    {"meaning":"development,growth","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"発達","answer":["はったつ"]},
    {"meaning":"announcement,publication","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"発表","answer":["はっぴょう"]},
    {"meaning":"invention","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"発明","answer":["はつめい"]},
    {"meaning":"to discuss,to talk together","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"話し合う","answer":["はなしあう"]},
    {"meaning":"to separate,to set free","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"放す","answer":["はなす"]},
    {"meaning":"mother","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"母親","answer":["ははおや"]},
    {"meaning":"scene,setting (e.g. of novel)","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"場面","answer":["ばめん"]},
    {"meaning":"abdomen,belly,stomach","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"腹","answer":["はら"]},
    {"meaning":"field,plain,prairie,tundra,moor,wilderness","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"原","answer":["はら","げん"]},
    {"meaning":"","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"番","answer":["ばん"]},
    {"meaning":"crime","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"犯罪","answer":["はんざい"]},
    {"meaning":"judgement,decision","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"判断","answer":["はんだん"]},
    {"meaning":"offender,criminal","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"犯人","answer":["はんにん"]},
    {"meaning":"aviation","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"飛行","answer":["ひこう"]},
    {"meaning":"emergency,extraordinary,unusual","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"非常","answer":["ひじょう"]},
    {"meaning":"beautiful person (woman)","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"美人","answer":["びじん"]},
    {"meaning":"date,dating","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"日付","answer":["ひづけ","かづけ"]},
    {"meaning":"inevitable death,desperation,frantic,inevitable result","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"必死","answer":["ひっし"]},
    {"meaning":"negation,denial,repudiation","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"否定","answer":["ひてい"]},
    {"meaning":"single word","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"一言","answer":["ひとこと","いちげん"]},
    {"meaning":"crowd of people","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"人込み","answer":["ひとごみ"]},
    {"meaning":"equal","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"等しい","answer":["ひとしい"]},
    {"meaning":"cost,expense","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"費用","answer":["ひよう"]},
    {"meaning":"table (e.g. Tab 1),chart,list","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"表","answer":["ひょう","おもて"]},
    {"meaning":"expression,presentation,representation (math)","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"表現","answer":["ひょうげん"]},
    {"meaning":"facial expression","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"表情","answer":["ひょうじょう"]},
    {"meaning":"equality (a),impartiality,evenness","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"平等","answer":["びょうどう"]},
    {"meaning":"surface,outside,face,appearance","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"表面","answer":["ひょうめん"]},
    {"meaning":"to spread (out),to extend,to stretch,to reach to,to get around","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"広がる","answer":["ひろがる"]},
    {"meaning":"way,means","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"便","answer":["びん"]},
    {"meaning":"un,non,negative prefix","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"不","answer":["ふ","ぶ"]},
    {"meaning":"anxiety,uneasiness,insecurity,suspense","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"不安","answer":["ふあん"]},
    {"meaning":"scenery","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"風景","answer":["ふうけい"]},
    {"meaning":"married couple,husband and wife","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"夫婦","answer":["ふうふ"]},
    {"meaning":"unhappiness,sorrow,misfortune,disaster,accident,death","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"不幸","answer":["ふこう"]},
    {"meaning":"mystery,curiosity","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"不思議","answer":["ふしぎ"]},
    {"meaning":"discomfort,disability,inconvenience,destitution","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"不自由","answer":["ふじゆう"]},
    {"meaning":"wife,Mrs,madam","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"夫人","answer":["ふじん"]},
    {"meaning":"woman,female","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"婦人","answer":["ふじん"]},
    {"meaning":"injustice,unfairness","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"不正","answer":["ふせい"]},
    {"meaning":"insufficiency,shortage,deficiency,lack,dearth","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"不足","answer":["ふそく"]},
    {"meaning":"stage (theatre)","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"舞台","answer":["ぶたい"]},
    {"meaning":"to hit,to strike","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"打つ","answer":["ぶつ","うつ"]},
    {"meaning":"material,substance","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"物質","answer":["ぶっしつ"]},
    {"meaning":"physics","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"物理","answer":["ぶつり"]},
    {"meaning":"ship,boat,watercraft,shipping,vessel,steamship","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"船","answer":["ふね"]},
    {"meaning":"complaint,discontent,dissatisfaction","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"不平","answer":["ふへい"]},
    {"meaning":"dissatisfaction,displeasure,discontent,complaints,unhappiness","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"不満","answer":["ふまん"]},
    {"meaning":"disadvantage,handicap,unfavorable,drawback","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"不利","answer":["ふり"]},
    {"meaning":"sentence","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"文","answer":["ぶん","ふみ"]},
    {"meaning":"civilization,culture","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"文明","answer":["ぶんめい"]},
    {"meaning":"peace,harmony","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"平和","answer":["へいわ"]},
    {"meaning":"(not) particularly,nothing","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"別に","answer":["べつに"]},
    {"meaning":"goblin,ghost,apparition,bugbear","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"変化","answer":["へんか"]},
    {"meaning":"to study","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"勉強","answer":["べんきょうする","べんきょう"]},
    {"meaning":"change,modification,alteration","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"変更","answer":["へんこう"]},
    {"meaning":"person, way of doing","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"方","answer":["かた","ほう"]},
    {"meaning":"Act (law: the X Act)","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"法","answer":["ほう"]},
    {"meaning":"direction,course,way","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"方向","answer":["ほうこう"]},
    {"meaning":"report,information","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"報告","answer":["ほうこく"]},
    {"meaning":"broadcast,broadcasting","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"放送","answer":["ほうそう"]},
    {"meaning":"method,manner,way,means,technique","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"方法","answer":["ほうほう"]},
    {"meaning":"call,visit","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"訪問","answer":["ほうもん"]},
    {"meaning":"Outside","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"外","answer":["そと","ほか"]},
    {"meaning":"degree,extent,bounds,limit","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"程","answer":["ほど"]},
    {"meaning":"footpath,walkway,sidewalk","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"歩道","answer":["ほどう"]},
    {"meaning":"truth,reality","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"本当","answer":["ほんと","ほんとう"]},
    {"meaning":"the person himself","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"本人","answer":["ほんにん"]},
    {"meaning":"genuine article","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"本物","answer":["ほんもの"]},
    {"meaning":"a space","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"間","answer":["あいだ","ま"]},
    {"meaning":"lost (stray) child","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"迷子","answer":["まいご"]},
    {"meaning":"to entrust to another,to leave to","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"任せる","answer":["まかせる"]},
    {"meaning":"defeat,loss,losing (a game)","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"負け","answer":["まけ"]},
    {"meaning":"diligent,serious,honest","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"真面目","answer":["まじめ"]},
    {"meaning":"to increase,to grow","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"増す","answer":["ます"]},
    {"meaning":"poor,needy","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"貧しい","answer":["まずしい"]},
    {"meaning":"yet,still,more,besides","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"未だ","answer":["まだ"]},
    {"meaning":"mistake","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"間違い","answer":["まちがい"]},
    {"meaning":"deep red,flushed (of face)","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"真っ赤","answer":["まっか"]},
    {"meaning":"straight (ahead),direct,upright","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"真っ直ぐ","answer":["まっすぐ"]},
    {"meaning":"really,truly,entirely,completely","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"全く","answer":["まったく"]},
    {"meaning":"to study (in depth),to learn,to take lessons in","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"学ぶ","answer":["まなぶ"]},
    {"meaning":"mimicry,imitation,behavior,pretense","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"真似","answer":["まね"]},
    {"meaning":"to invite","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"招く","answer":["まねく"]},
    {"meaning":"to protect,to obey,to guard,to abide (by the rules)","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"守る","answer":["まもる"]},
    {"meaning":"to turn,to revolve","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"回す","answer":["まわす"]},
    {"meaning":"circumference,surroundings,circulation","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"回り","answer":["まわり"]},
    {"meaning":"by some chance,by some possibility,if by any chance,10E4:1 odds","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"万一","answer":["まんいち"]},
    {"meaning":"satisfaction","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"満足","answer":["まんぞく"]},
    {"meaning":"fruit,nut,seed,content,good result","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"実","answer":["み","じつ"]},
    {"meaning":"seeing one off,farewell,escort","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"見送り","answer":["みおくり"]},
    {"meaning":"friend,ally,supporter","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"味方","answer":["みかた"]},
    {"meaning":"splendid,magnificent,beautiful,admirable","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"見事","answer":["みごと"]},
    {"meaning":"to be full,to rise (tide),to mature,to expire","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"満ちる","answer":["みちる"]},
    {"meaning":"to recognize,to appreciate,to approve,to admit,to notice","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"認める","answer":["みとめる","したためる"]},
    {"meaning":"all,everyone,everybody","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"皆","answer":["みんな","みな"]},
    {"meaning":"enquiry,expression of sympathy,expression of concern","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"見舞い","answer":["みまい"]},
    {"meaning":"present,souvenir","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"土産","answer":["みやげ","どさん"]},
    {"meaning":"capital","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"都","answer":["みやこ","と"]},
    {"meaning":"day after tomorrow","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"明後日","answer":["みょうごにち","あさって"]},
    {"meaning":"future (life, tense)","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"未来","answer":["みらい"]},
    {"meaning":"charm,fascination,glamour","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"魅力","answer":["みりょく"]},
    {"meaning":"to see, to watch","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"見る","answer":["みる"]},
    {"meaning":"facing,opposite,across the street,other side","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"向かい","answer":["むかい"]},
    {"meaning":"meeting,person sent to pick up an arrival","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"迎え","answer":["むかえ"]},
    {"meaning":"to face","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"向く","answer":["むく"]},
    {"meaning":"to turn towards,to point","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"向ける","answer":["むける"]},
    {"meaning":"daze,(in a) trance,ecstasy,delirium,engrossment","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"夢中","answer":["むちゅう"]},
    {"meaning":"clear up,clarify,define","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"明確","answer":["めいかく"]},
    {"meaning":"to order,to command,to appoint","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"命じる","answer":["めいじる"]},
    {"meaning":"master,expert","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"名人","answer":["めいじん"]},
    {"meaning":"trouble,difficulty,care,attention","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"面倒","answer":["めんどう"]},
    {"meaning":"to apply for,to make an application","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"申し込む","answer":["もうしこむ"]},
    {"meaning":"letter (of alphabet),character","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"文字","answer":["もじ","もんじ"]},
    {"meaning":"to raise,to lift up,to flatter","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"持ち上げる","answer":["もちあげる"]},
    {"meaning":"to use,to make use of","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"用いる","answer":["もちいる"]},
    {"meaning":"most,extremely","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"最も","answer":["もっとも"]},
    {"meaning":"(1) origin,original,(2) former","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"元","answer":["もと"]},
    {"meaning":"to restore,to put back,to return","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"戻す","answer":["もどす"]},
    {"meaning":"to seek,to request,to demand,to want,to wish for,to search for,to pursue (pleasure),to hunt (a job),","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"求める","answer":["もとめる"]},
    {"meaning":"person","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"者","answer":["もの"]},
    {"meaning":"sounds","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"物音","answer":["ものおと"]},
    {"meaning":"tale,story,legend","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"物語","answer":["ものがたり"]},
    {"meaning":"things,everything","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"物事","answer":["ものごと"]},
    {"meaning":"use,service,role,position","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"役","answer":["やく","えき"]},
    {"meaning":"approximately,about,some","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"約","answer":["やく"]},
    {"meaning":"part,assigning (allotment of) parts,role,duties","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"役割","answer":["やくわり"]},
    {"meaning":"inn,lodging","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"宿","answer":["やど"]},
    {"meaning":"to tear,to violate,to defeat,to smash,to destroy","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"破る","answer":["やぶる"]},
    {"meaning":"to retire","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"辞める","answer":["やめる"]},
    {"meaning":"overall victory,championship","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"優勝","answer":["ゆうしょう"]},
    {"meaning":"friendship,fellowship","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"友情","answer":["ゆうじょう"]},
    {"meaning":"friend","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"友人","answer":["ゆうじん"]},
    {"meaning":"able,capable,efficient,skill","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"有能","answer":["ゆうのう"]},
    {"meaning":"evening","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"夕べ","answer":["ゆうべ"]},
    {"meaning":"advantageous,better,profitable,lucrative","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"有利","answer":["ゆうり"]},
    {"meaning":"to permit,to allow,to approve","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"許す","answer":["ゆるす"]},
    {"meaning":"evening,night","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"夜","answer":["よる","よ"]},
    {"meaning":"dawn,daybreak","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"夜明け","answer":["よあけ"]},
    {"meaning":"way,manner,kind","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"様","answer":["よう","さま"]},
    {"meaning":"easy,simple,plain","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"容易","answer":["ようい"]},
    {"meaning":"season,weather,cheerfulness","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"陽気","answer":["ようき"]},
    {"meaning":"request,demand,requisition","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"要求","answer":["ようきゅう"]},
    {"meaning":"care,precaution,guarding,caution","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"用心","answer":["ようじん"]},
    {"meaning":"aspect,state,appearance","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"様子","answer":["ようす"]},
    {"meaning":"in a word,after all,the point is ..,in short ..","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"要するに","answer":["ようするに"]},
    {"meaning":"gist,main point","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"要点","answer":["ようてん"]},
    {"meaning":"What day of the week?","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"何曜日","answer":["なんようび"]},
    {"meaning":"expectation,assume will happen,forecast","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"予期","answer":["よき"]},
    {"meaning":"to cross (e.g. arms),to traverse","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"横切る","answer":["よこぎる"]},
    {"meaning":"midnight,dead of night","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"夜中","answer":["よなか","やちゅう"]},
    {"meaning":"society,the world,the times","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"世の中","answer":["よのなか"]},
    {"meaning":"forecast,prediction","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"予報","answer":["よほう"]},
    {"meaning":"prevention,precaution,protection against","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"予防","answer":["よぼう"]},
    {"meaning":"reading","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"読み","answer":["よみ"]},
    {"meaning":"(a) joy,(a) delight,rapture,pleasure,gratification,rejoicing,congratulations,felicitations","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"喜び","answer":["よろこび"]},
    {"meaning":",for (10 days),next (year)","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"来","answer":["らい"]},
    {"meaning":"comfort,ease","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"楽","answer":["らく"]},
    {"meaning":"understanding,comprehension","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"理解","answer":["りかい"]},
    {"meaning":"clever,shrewd,bright,sharp,wise,intelligent","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"利口","answer":["りこう"]},
    {"meaning":"divorce","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"離婚","answer":["りこん"]},
    {"meaning":"ideal","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"理想","answer":["りそう"]},
    {"meaning":"studying abroad","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"留学","answer":["りゅうがく"]},
    {"meaning":"fashionable,fad,in vogue,prevailing","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"流行","answer":["りゅうこう","はやり"]},
    {"meaning":"fee,charge,fare","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"料金","answer":["りょうきん"]},
    {"meaning":"instance,example,case","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"例","answer":["れい","ためし"]},
    {"meaning":"expression of gratitude","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"礼","answer":["れい"]},
    {"meaning":"calm,composure,coolness,serenity","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"冷静","answer":["れいせい"]},
    {"meaning":"queue,line,row","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"列","answer":["れつ"]},
    {"meaning":"train (ordinary)","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"列車","answer":["れっしゃ"]},
    {"meaning":"association (of ideas),suggestion","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"連想","answer":["れんそう"]},
    {"meaning":"serial,consecutive,continuity,continuing","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"連続","answer":["れんぞく"]},
    {"meaning":"the aged,old person","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"老人","answer":["ろうじん"]},
    {"meaning":"manual labor,toil,work","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"労働","answer":["ろうどう"]},
    {"meaning":"to argue,to discuss,to debate","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"論じる","answer":["ろんじる"]},
    {"meaning":"controversy,dispute","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"論争","answer":["ろんそう"]},
    {"meaning":"thesis,essay,treatise,paper","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"論文","answer":["ろんぶん"]},
    {"meaning":"parting,separation,farewell","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"別れ","answer":["わかれ"]},
    {"meaning":"topic,subject","kanjiLevel":5,"question":"話題","answer":["わだい"]},
    {"meaning":"laugh,laughter,smile","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"笑い","answer":["わらい"]},
    {"meaning":"to divide,to cut,to break,to halve","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"割る","answer":["わる"]},
    {"meaning":"abuse,insult,slander,evil speaking","kanjiLevel":4,"question":"悪口","answer":["わるくち","わるぐち","あっこう"]},
    {"meaning":"to match","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"合う","answer":["あう"]},
    {"meaning":"play","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"遊び","answer":["あそび"]},
    {"meaning":"safety","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"安全","answer":["あんぜん"]},
    {"meaning":"stone","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"石","answer":["いし"]},
    {"meaning":"within","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"以内","answer":["いない"]},
    {"meaning":"receipt","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"受付","answer":["うけつけ"]},
    {"meaning":"to take a lesson or test","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"受ける","answer":["うける"]},
    {"meaning":"beautiful","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"美しい","answer":["うつくしい"]},
    {"meaning":"to choose","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"選ぶ","answer":["えらぶ"]},
    {"meaning":"to be late","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"遅れる","answer":["おくれる"]},
    {"meaning":"to get angry,to be angry","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"怒る","answer":["おこる","いかる"]},
    {"meaning":"closet","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"押し入れ","answer":["おしいれ"]},
    {"meaning":"(polite) your house","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"お宅","answer":["おたく"]},
    {"meaning":"to fall or drop","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"落ちる","answer":["おちる"]},
    {"meaning":"husband","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"夫","answer":["おっと"]},
    {"meaning":"to drop","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"落とす","answer":["おとす"]},
    {"meaning":"calling on someone who is ill,enquiry","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"お見舞い","answer":["おみまい"]},
    {"meaning":"souvenir","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"お土産","answer":["おみやげ"]},
    {"meaning":"to break or to fold","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"折る","answer":["おる"]},
    {"meaning":"expression of gratitude","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"お礼","answer":["おれい"]},
    {"meaning":"to break or be folded","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"折れる","answer":["おれる"]},
    {"meaning":"meeting","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"会議","answer":["かいぎ"]},
    {"meaning":"meeting room","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"会議室","answer":["かいぎしつ"]},
    {"meaning":"to change","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"変える","answer":["かえる"]},
    {"meaning":"science","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"科学","answer":["かがく"]},
    {"meaning":"to hang something","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"掛ける","answer":["かける"]},
    {"meaning":"shape","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"形","answer":["かたち"]},
    {"meaning":"to win","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"勝つ","answer":["かつ"]},
    {"meaning":"housewife","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"家内","answer":["かない"]},
    {"meaning":"sad","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"悲しい","answer":["かなしい"]},
    {"meaning":"certainly,necessarily","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"必ず","answer":["かならず"]},
    {"meaning":"she,girlfriend","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"彼女","answer":["かのじょ"]},
    {"meaning":"he,boyfriend","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"彼","answer":["かれ"]},
    {"meaning":"they","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"彼ら","answer":["かれら"]},
    {"meaning":"to change","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"変わる","answer":["かわる"]},
    {"meaning":"relationship","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"関係","answer":["かんけい"]},
    {"meaning":"opportunity","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"機会","answer":["きかい"]},
    {"meaning":"danger","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"危険","answer":["きけん"]},
    {"meaning":"to be decided","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"決る","answer":["きまる"]},
    {"meaning":"(informal) You (used by men towards women)","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"君","answer":["きみ","くん"]},
    {"meaning":"to decide","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"決める","answer":["きめる"]},
    {"meaning":"guest,customer","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"客","answer":["きゃく"]},
    {"meaning":"education","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"教育","answer":["きょういく"]},
    {"meaning":"neighbourhood","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"近所","answer":["きんじょ"]},
    {"meaning":"condition,health","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"具合","answer":["ぐあい"]},
    {"meaning":"airport","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"空港","answer":["くうこう"]},
    {"meaning":"grass","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"草","answer":["くさ"]},
    {"meaning":"to get dark,to come to an end","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"暮れる","answer":["くれる"]},
    {"meaning":"finance,economy","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"経済","answer":["けいざい"]},
    {"meaning":"police","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"警察","answer":["けいさつ"]},
    {"meaning":"scene,landscape","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"景色","answer":["けしき"]},
    {"meaning":"eraser","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"消しゴム","answer":["けしゴム","けしごむ"]},
    {"meaning":"lodging","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"下宿","answer":["げしゅく"]},
    {"meaning":"never","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"決して","answer":["けっして"]},
    {"meaning":"cause,source","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"原因","answer":["げんいん"]},
    {"meaning":"traffic,transportation","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"交通","answer":["こうつう"]},
    {"meaning":"high school","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"高等学校","answer":["こうとうがっこう"]},
    {"meaning":"government worker","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"公務員","answer":["こうむいん"]},
    {"meaning":"(honorable) your husband","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"御主人","answer":["ごしゅじん"]},
    {"meaning":"knowing,acquaintance","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"ご存じ","answer":["ごぞんじ"]},
    {"meaning":"to be crowded","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"込む","answer":["こむ"]},
    {"meaning":"uncooked rice","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"米","answer":["こめ"]},
    {"meaning":"frightening","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"怖い","answer":["こわい"]},
    {"meaning":"latest,nowadays","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"最近","answer":["さいきん"]},
    {"meaning":"last,end","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"最後","answer":["さいご"]},
    {"meaning":"beginning,first","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"最初","answer":["さいしょ"]},
    {"meaning":"to look for","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"探す","answer":["さがす"]},
    {"meaning":"(polite) to give","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"差し上げる","answer":["さしあげる"]},
    {"meaning":"industry","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"産業","answer":["さんぎょう"]},
    {"meaning":"disappointment","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"残念","answer":["ざんねん"]},
    {"meaning":"city","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"市","answer":["し","いち"]},
    {"meaning":"match,game","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"試合","answer":["しあい"]},
    {"meaning":"failure,mistake","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"失敗","answer":["しっぱい"]},
    {"meaning":"citizen","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"市民","answer":["しみん"]},
    {"meaning":"office","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"事務所","answer":["じむしょ"]},
    {"meaning":"freedom","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"自由","answer":["じゆう"]},
    {"meaning":"custom,manners","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"習慣","answer":["しゅうかん"]},
    {"meaning":"an address,a residence","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"住所","answer":["じゅうしょ"]},
    {"meaning":"novel","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"小説","answer":["しょうせつ"]},
    {"meaning":"woman","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"女性","answer":["じょせい"]},
    {"meaning":"to investigate","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"調べる","answer":["しらべる"]},
    {"meaning":"Shinto shrine","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"神社","answer":["じんじゃ"]},
    {"meaning":"swimming","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"水泳","answer":["すいえい"]},
    {"meaning":"mathematics,arithmetic","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"数学","answer":["すうがく"]},
    {"meaning":"to exceed","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"過ぎる","answer":["すぎる"]},
    {"meaning":"to make progress","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"進む","answer":["すすむ"]},
    {"meaning":"to finish","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"済む","answer":["すむ"]},
    {"meaning":"to live","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"生活","answer":["せいかつ"]},
    {"meaning":"politics,government","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"政治","answer":["せいじ"]},
    {"meaning":"seat","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"席","answer":["せき"]},
    {"meaning":"explanation","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"説明","answer":["せつめい"]},
    {"meaning":"back of the body","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"背中","answer":["せなか"]},
    {"meaning":"war","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"戦争","answer":["せんそう"]},
    {"meaning":"to rear,to bring up","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"育てる","answer":["そだてる"]},
    {"meaning":"grandfather","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"祖父","answer":["そふ"]},
    {"meaning":"grandmother","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"祖母","answer":["そぼ"]},
    {"meaning":"to leave hospital","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"退院","answer":["たいいん"]},
    {"meaning":"to break down","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"倒れる","answer":["たおれる"]},
    {"meaning":"definite","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"確か","answer":["たしか"]},
    {"meaning":"to visit","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"訪ねる","answer":["たずねる"]},
    {"meaning":"for example","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"例えば","answer":["たとえば"]},
    {"meaning":"male","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"男性","answer":["だんせい"]},
    {"meaning":"to seize","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"捕まえる","answer":["つかまえる"]},
    {"meaning":"to be attached","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"付く","answer":["つく"]},
    {"meaning":"circumstances,convenience","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"都合","answer":["つごう"]},
    {"meaning":"to report","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"伝える","answer":["つたえる"]},
    {"meaning":"to be continued","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"続く","answer":["つづく"]},
    {"meaning":"to continue","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"続ける","answer":["つづける"]},
    {"meaning":"(humble) wife","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"妻","answer":["つま"]},
    {"meaning":"to lead","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"連れる","answer":["つれる"]},
    {"meaning":"suitability","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"適当","answer":["てきとう"]},
    {"meaning":"to assist","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"手伝う","answer":["てつだう"]},
    {"meaning":"point,dot","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"点","answer":["てん"]},
    {"meaning":"weather forecast","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"天気予報","answer":["てんきよほう"]},
    {"meaning":"telegram","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"電報","answer":["でんぽう"]},
    {"meaning":"tool,means","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"道具","answer":["どうぐ"]},
    {"meaning":"zoo","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"動物園","answer":["どうぶつえん"]},
    {"meaning":"distant","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"遠く","answer":["とおく"]},
    {"meaning":"on the way","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"途中","answer":["とちゅう","つちゅう"]},
    {"meaning":"to fix,to repair","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"直す","answer":["なおす"]},
    {"meaning":"to be fixed,to be repaired","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"直る","answer":["なおる"]},
    {"meaning":"to be cured,to heal","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"治る","answer":["なおる"]},
    {"meaning":"to die","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"亡くなる","answer":["なくなる"]},
    {"meaning":"to throw or cast away","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"投げる","answer":["なげる"]},
    {"meaning":"to grow accustomed to","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"慣れる","answer":["なれる"]},
    {"meaning":"bitter","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"苦い","answer":["にがい"]},
    {"meaning":"to escape","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"逃げる","answer":["にげる"]},
    {"meaning":"journal","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"日記","answer":["にっき"]},
    {"meaning":"to be similar","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"似る","answer":["にる"]},
    {"meaning":"doll, figure","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"人形","answer":["にんぎょう"]},
    {"meaning":"to steal","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"盗む","answer":["ぬすむ"]},
    {"meaning":"fever","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"熱","answer":["ねつ"]},
    {"meaning":"sleepy","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"眠い","answer":["ねむい"]},
    {"meaning":"to sleep","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"眠る","answer":["ねむる"]},
    {"meaning":"to remain","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"残る","answer":["のこる"]},
    {"meaning":"vehicle","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"乗り物","answer":["のりもの"]},
    {"meaning":"leaf","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"葉","answer":["は"]},
    {"meaning":"situation","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"場合","answer":["ばあい"]},
    {"meaning":"dentist","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"歯医者","answer":["はいしゃ"]},
    {"meaning":"location","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"場所","answer":["ばしょ"]},
    {"meaning":"embarrassed","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"恥ずかしい","answer":["はずかしい"]},
    {"meaning":"to pay","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"払う","answer":["はらう"]},
    {"meaning":"television or radio program","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"番組","answer":["ばんぐみ"]},
    {"meaning":"opposition","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"反対","answer":["はんたい"]},
    {"meaning":"to grow cold","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"冷える","answer":["ひえる"]},
    {"meaning":"light","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"光","answer":["ひかり"]},
    {"meaning":"to shine,to glitter","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"光る","answer":["ひかる"]},
    {"meaning":"drawer,drawing out","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"引き出し","answer":["ひきだし"]},
    {"meaning":"to withdraw","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"引き出す","answer":["ひきだす"]},
    {"meaning":"art gallery","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"美術館","answer":["びじゅつかん"]},
    {"meaning":"extremely","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"非常に","answer":["ひじょうに"]},
    {"meaning":"to move house","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"引っ越す","answer":["ひっこす"]},
    {"meaning":"necessary","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"必要","answer":["ひつよう"]},
    {"meaning":"to increase","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"増える","answer":["ふえる"]},
    {"meaning":"deep","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"深い","answer":["ふかい"]},
    {"meaning":"head of a section","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"部長","answer":["ぶちょう"]},
    {"meaning":"to become fat","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"太る","answer":["ふとる"]},
    {"meaning":"inconvenience","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"不便","answer":["ふべん","ふびん"]},
    {"meaning":"culture","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"文化","answer":["ぶんか"]},
    {"meaning":"grammar","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"文法","answer":["ぶんぽう"]},
    {"meaning":"strange","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"変","answer":["へん"]},
    {"meaning":"reply","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"返事","answer":["へんじ"]},
    {"meaning":"(humble) to go,to come","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"参る","answer":["まいる"]},
    {"meaning":"to lose","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"負ける","answer":["まける"]},
    {"meaning":"to make a mistake","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"間違える","answer":["まちがえる"]},
    {"meaning":"to be in time for","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"間に合う","answer":["まにあう"]},
    {"meaning":"to go around","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"回る","answer":["まわる"]},
    {"meaning":"harbour","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"港","answer":["みなと"]},
    {"meaning":"to face","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"向かう","answer":["むかう"]},
    {"meaning":"to go out to meet","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"迎える","answer":["むかえる"]},
    {"meaning":"olden days, former","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"昔","answer":["むかし"]},
    {"meaning":"(humble) son","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"息子","answer":["むすこ"]},
    {"meaning":"(humble) daughter","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"娘","answer":["むすめ"]},
    {"meaning":"(humble) to say,to tell","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"申し上げる","answer":["もうしあげる"]},
    {"meaning":"(humble) to be called,to say","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"申す","answer":["もうす"]},
    {"meaning":"to turn back","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"戻る","answer":["もどる"]},
    {"meaning":"promise","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"約束","answer":["やくそく"]},
    {"meaning":"to be helpful","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"役に立つ","answer":["やくにたつ"]},
    {"meaning":"kind","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"優しい","answer":["やさしい"]},
    {"meaning":"finger","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"指","answer":["ゆび"]},
    {"meaning":"dream","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"夢","answer":["ゆめ"]},
    {"meaning":"preparation for a lesson","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"予習","answer":["よしゅう"]},
    {"meaning":"arrangement","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"予定","answer":["よてい"]},
    {"meaning":"reservation","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"予約","answer":["よやく"]},
    {"meaning":"to visit","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"寄る","answer":["よる"]},
    {"meaning":"to be delighted","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"喜ぶ","answer":["よろこぶ"]},
    {"meaning":"reason","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"理由","answer":["りゆう"]},
    {"meaning":"utilization","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"利用","answer":["りよう"]},
    {"meaning":"both sides","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"両方","answer":["りょうほう"]},
    {"meaning":"absence","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"留守","answer":["るす"]},
    {"meaning":"lost article","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"忘れ物","answer":["わすれもの"]},
    {"meaning":"to laugh,to smile","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"笑う","answer":["わらう"]},
    {"meaning":"rate,ratio,percentage","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"割合","answer":["わりあい"]},
    {"meaning":"to break","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"割れる","answer":["われる"]},
    {"meaning":"way of swimming","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"泳ぎ方","answer":["およぎかた"]},
    {"meaning":"breakfast","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"朝御飯","answer":["あさごはん"]},
    {"meaning":"to play, to make a visit","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"遊ぶ","answer":["あそぶ"]},
    {"meaning":"hot to the touch","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"熱い","answer":["あつい"]},
    {"meaning":"dangerous","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"危ない","answer":["あぶない"]},
    {"meaning":"to wash","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"洗う","answer":["あらう"]},
    {"meaning":"busy, irritated","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"忙しい","answer":["いそがしい"]},
    {"meaning":"painful","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"痛い","answer":["いたい"]},
    {"meaning":"together","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"一緒","answer":["いっしょ"]},
    {"meaning":"to be, to have (used for people and animals)","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"居る","answer":["いる","おる"]},
    {"meaning":"picture","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"絵","answer":["え"]},
    {"meaning":"to put","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"置く","answer":["おく"]},
    {"meaning":"alcohol, rice wine","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"お酒","answer":["おさけ"]},
    {"meaning":"to push, to stamp something","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"押す","answer":["おす"]},
    {"meaning":"late, slow","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"遅い","answer":["おそい"]},
    {"meaning":"bathroom","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"お手洗い","answer":["おてあらい"]},
    {"meaning":"day before yesterday","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"一昨日","answer":["おととい","いっさくじつ"]},
    {"meaning":"year before last","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"一昨年","answer":["おととし","いっさくねん"]},
    {"meaning":"to remember","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"覚える","answer":["おぼえる"]},
    {"meaning":"to swim","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"泳ぐ","answer":["およぐ"]},
    {"meaning":"Stairs","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"階段","answer":["かいだん"]},
    {"meaning":"to return something","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"返す","answer":["かえす"]},
    {"meaning":"Household","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"家庭","answer":["かてい"]},
    {"meaning":"to disappear","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"消える","answer":["きえる"]},
    {"meaning":"Yesterday","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"昨日","answer":["きのう"]},
    {"meaning":"medicine","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"薬","answer":["くすり"]},
    {"meaning":"Fruit","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"果物","answer":["くだもの"]},
    {"meaning":"Gloomy","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"暗い","answer":["くらい"]},
    {"meaning":"policeman","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"警官","answer":["けいかん"]},
    {"meaning":"to erase, to turn off power","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"消す","answer":["けす"]},
    {"meaning":"Park","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"公園","answer":["こうえん"]},
    {"meaning":"intersection","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"交差点","answer":["こうさてん"]},
    {"meaning":"police box","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"交番","answer":["こうばん"]},
    {"meaning":"Voice","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"声","answer":["こえ"]},
    {"meaning":"word, language","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"言葉","answer":["ことば"]},
    {"meaning":"Child","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"子供","answer":["こども"]},
    {"meaning":"cooked rice, meal","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"御飯","answer":["ごはん"]},
    {"meaning":"to be worried","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"困る","answer":["こまる"]},
    {"meaning":"this evening","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"今晩","answer":["こんばん"]},
    {"meaning":"to stretch out hands, to raise an umbrella","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"差す","answer":["さす"]},
    {"meaning":"Cold","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"寒い","answer":["さむい"]},
    {"meaning":"Dictionary","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"辞書","answer":["じしょ"]},
    {"meaning":"Dictionary","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"字引","answer":["じびき"]},
    {"meaning":"to close, to be closed","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"閉まる","answer":["しまる"]},
    {"meaning":"to close something","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"閉める","answer":["しめる"]},
    {"meaning":"homework","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"宿題","answer":["しゅくだい"]},
    {"meaning":"to smoke, to suck","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"吸う","answer":["すう"]},
    {"meaning":"Likeable","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"好き","answer":["すき"]},
    {"meaning":"to sit","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"座る","answer":["すわる"]},
    {"meaning":"Pupil","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"生徒","answer":["せいと"]},
    {"meaning":"business suit","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"背広","answer":["せびろ"]},
    {"meaning":"All","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"全部","answer":["ぜんぶ"]},
    {"meaning":"to be very likeable","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"大好き","answer":["だいすき"]},
    {"meaning":"kitchen","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"台所","answer":["だいどころ"]},
    {"meaning":"to differ","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"違う","answer":["ちがう"]},
    {"meaning":"to get tired","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"疲れる","answer":["つかれる"]},
    {"meaning":"next","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"次","answer":["つぎ"]},
    {"meaning":"to work for someone","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"勤める","answer":["つとめる"]},
    {"meaning":"cold to the touch","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"冷たい","answer":["つめたい"]},
    {"meaning":"far","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"遠い","answer":["とおい"]},
    {"meaning":"place","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"所","answer":["ところ"]},
    {"meaning":"friend","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"友達","answer":["ともだち"]},
    {"meaning":"to take something","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"取る","answer":["とる"]},
    {"meaning":"garden","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"庭","answer":["にわ"]},
    {"meaning":"cat","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"猫","answer":["ねこ"]},
    {"meaning":"to go to bed,to sleep","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"寝る","answer":["ねる"]},
    {"meaning":"to climb","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"登る","answer":["のぼる"]},
    {"meaning":"to get on,to ride","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"乗る","answer":["のる"]},
    {"meaning":"tooth","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"歯","answer":["は"]},
    {"meaning":"postcard","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"葉書","answer":["はがき"]},
    {"meaning":"box","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"箱","answer":["はこ"]},
    {"meaning":"beginning","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"初め","answer":["はじめ"]},
    {"meaning":"for the first time","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"初めて","answer":["はじめて"]},
    {"meaning":"20 years old,20th year","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"二十歳","answer":["はたち"]},
    {"meaning":"to work","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"働く","answer":["はたらく"]},
    {"meaning":"quick","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"速い","answer":["はやい"]},
    {"meaning":"clear weather","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"晴れ","answer":["はれ"]},
    {"meaning":"to be sunny","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"晴れる","answer":["はれる"]},
    {"meaning":"evening","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"晩","answer":["ばん"]},
    {"meaning":"number","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"番号","answer":["ばんごう"]},
    {"meaning":"evening meal","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"晩御飯","answer":["ばんごはん"]},
    {"meaning":"to pull","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"引く","answer":["ひく"]},
    {"meaning":"aeroplane","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"飛行機","answer":["ひこうき"]},
    {"meaning":"midday meal","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"昼御飯","answer":["ひるごはん"]},
    {"meaning":"to blow","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"吹く","answer":["ふく"]},
    {"meaning":"fat","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"太い","answer":["ふとい"]},
    {"meaning":"room","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"部屋","answer":["へや"]},
    {"meaning":"useful, convenient","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"便利","answer":["べんり"]},
    {"meaning":"want","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"欲しい","answer":["ほしい"]},
    {"meaning":"every night","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"毎晩","answer":["まいばん"]},
    {"meaning":"to turn,to bend","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"曲る","answer":["まがる"]},
    {"meaning":"window","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"窓","answer":["まど"]},
    {"meaning":"everyone","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"皆さん","answer":["みなさん"]},
    {"meaning":"ear","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"耳","answer":["みみ"]},
    {"meaning":"to see, to watch","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"観る","answer":["みる"]},
    {"meaning":"over there","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"向こう","answer":["むこう"]},
    {"meaning":"easy, simple","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"易しい","answer":["やさしい"]},
    {"meaning":"last night","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"昨夜","answer":["ゆうべ","さくや"]},
    {"meaning":"beside,side,width","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"横","answer":["よこ"]},
    {"meaning":"to call out,to invite","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"呼ぶ","answer":["よぶ"]},
    {"meaning":"overseas student","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"留学生","answer":["りゅうがくせい"]},
    {"meaning":"both parents","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"両親","answer":["りょうしん"]},
    {"meaning":"young","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"若い","answer":["わかい"]},
    {"meaning":"to forget","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"忘れる","answer":["わすれる"]},
    {"meaning":"to hand over","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"渡す","answer":["わたす"]},
    {"meaning":"to go across","kanjiLevel":3,"question":"渡る","answer":["わたる"]}
  ]}

